











#### Portfolio

https://prapask.wordpress.com https://barrimos.github.io

#### **GOAL**

Web developer & Designer

### INTRODUCE

Let's start with graphic designer for 7 years with extensive experiences in print design poster name card and banner.

I am ambitious and curious new things, not to good talker but good to listener, Expect to working in tech area with very talented team. I have a passionate to Artificial intelligence to create innovative or combination of tech and design together for better results.

### WORK EXPERIENCES

- 2020 Present Enhancing skills in web development React (typescript), Node.js DSA through online courses and self-study.
- Projects web application supports all screen sizes
  - Matrix calculator html, scss, javascript, python

With various methods such as Determinant, Transpose, Cofactor, Identity, and Inverse. Displayed in mathematical matrix format

- Maze game html, scss, javascript
  - A maze game using algorithms like BFS, Greedy BFS, Dijkstra, and A\* for maze stage generation and solving.
- Algo arithmetic puzzle game html, scss, javascript
  - A Japanese card-based puzzle game designed to simulate playing on a table, allowing users to pick, drag, and drop cards.
- LomwongChat Real-time chatting Mern stack, Redis, SocketlO
  - With features like user registration, creating public or private chat rooms, notifications, and reporting.

· Graphic Designer	@ OSCAR GRAPHIC	Contact for 3 months.	(DEC 2019 - FEB 2020)

Responsibilities - Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner, poster, sticker label and namecard.

- Produce some work pieces as well.

Achievements - Many clients trust and let me to be partner on new projects again.

• Coordinator Designer @ DKSH (Thailand) Probation for 5 months. (NOV 2018 - APR 2019)

Responsibilities - Design events area to set position of furniture.

- Control the installation before the event day.

- Supports senior designer.

Achievements - Design the space to place the product shelves in the event area to display products appropriately,

prominently, and continuously for people walking to view the products.

• Graphic Designer @ SIAM PARAGON DEVELOPMENT Officer for 6 years. (JUN 2012 - APR 2018)

Responsibilities - Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner, poster and photo backdrop.

- Production control check pantone colour before produce.

Achievements - To be a part of team that create big project in the mall make a good experience for customers

via graphic design and print media.

- Reduce the cost of hiring an agency.

## **CERTIFICATES**

· Certification of junior Software Developer Program (2022) a 12-week-full-time bootcamp : Generation Thailand

# COURSES

• Junior software developer : MERN stack technology @ Generation Thailand. 1/2022 - 4/2022 : 3 months

- Learned how to build web applications from React as front-end, Node.js as back end, and MongoDB as a Database.

- Learned essential skills for switching careers, such as growth mindset, communication, agile, and teamwork.

- Learned bihavioral skills to be a good worker.

Web develop : HTML CSS PHP SQL @ Tutortong.
Basic 3d model sculpting : Zbrush @ Z-LA digital arts.
Basic 3ds Max model and lighting : 3ds Max @ Utahtd 3d tutor.
5/2019 - 7/2019 : 3 months
B months
Basic 3ds Max model and lighting : 3ds Max @ Utahtd 3d tutor.
5/2018 - 7/2018 : 3 months

## **EDUCATION**